Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
- Series C: Harvard University GSD, Administrative Affairs: Publications and Exhibitions, / Date(s): 1960-1989 (bulk) -- 1955-2006 (inclusive); C000; / Quantity: 4 boxes / Dimensions: 4 linear ft. / Medium: varies / Support: varies
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d. (1980s-1990s); Folder: CC080; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic copies / Support: paper
    Note: Items included in folders CF080 through CF114 are line drawings and other art drawings kept by the Exhibitions Department, probably for use in exhibitions. They may also represent the development of art items produced specifically for exhibitions. Some are attached to a name, others are not. Many from folder labeled "Miscellaneous Projects / Line Art."
    Note: Several xerographic copies of a contour drawing of the griffins that originally stood on the roof of Hunt Hall, and were later relocated next to the entrance door to Gund Hall on Quincy Street.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC081; / Quantity: 27 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic copies; ink / Support: paper; board
    Note: Several xerographic copies of typography most probably used for an exhibition. Also includes contour drawings of the griffins mentioned above.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC082; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 13" x 10" / Medium: negative / Support: acetate
    Note: Negative of contour drawing of griffin mentioned in CF080.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC083; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 12" x 10" / Medium: photostat / Support: paper
    Note: Two inverted photostats of contour drawing of griffin mentioned in CF080.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC084; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 12" x 10" / Medium: negative / Support: acetate
    Note: Photostat of contour drawing of griffin mentioned in CF080.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: CC085; / Quantity: 19 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: ink; xerographic reproductions / Support: trace; paper
    Note: Miscellaneous drawings and line art, some apparently for use in a GSD Holiday card (1996).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC086; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 9" x 12-1/2" / Medium: photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Photostats with floor plans of Gund Hall.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC087; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 9" x 12-1/2" / Medium: ink; xerographic copies / Support: mylar; paper
    Note: Diagram showing location of 7 Sumner Rd. in relation to Gund Hall.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC088; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 14" x 11" / Medium: photostat / Support: paper
    Note: Photostat of location of Harvard Yard in relation to Harvard Square and the Charles.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC089; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 9-1/2" x 12" / Medium: photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Photostats with miscellaneous sketches (line art).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC090; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 12" x 10"; 9" x 9" / Medium: photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous photostats of line art used by the exhibitions department.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1993; Folder: CC091; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 11" x 17" / Medium: photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous photostats.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1993; Folder: CC092; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 17" / Medium: xerographic reproduction / Support: paper
    Note: Xerographic reproduction of elevation of Haystack Mountain by Edward Larrabee Barnes, probably for exhibition and/or publication.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1993; Folder: CC093; / Quantity: 25 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Notebook on Han's Scharoun's Berlin Philharmonic Hall. Every year the GSD used to select a group of students to visit a work of architecture, either contemporary or "historical", in order to study and record it. The projects that resulted were displayed in an exhibition made by those students in conjunction with the Department of Lectures and Exhibitions. This notebook consists of some of those proposals.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC094; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 6" x 6" / Medium: ink; photostats / Support: trace; paper
    Note: Draft sketches of Gund Hall.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC095; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Photostats with drawing of thistle leaf (probably for Holiday card).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1999; Folder: CC096; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 6" x 6"; 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: ink / Support: trace; paper
    Note: Sketches labeled "by Bill Hubner." Groton School, Faculty Housing, Proposed Siting.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC097; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic copies / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous xerographic copies of line art items to be used in publications / exhibitions.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC098; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic copies / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous xerographic copies of sketches / line art items (Gary Hildebrand) to be used in publications / exhibitions.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC099; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic copies / Support: paper
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC100; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic copies / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous xerographic copies of sketches / line art items (Niall Kirkwood) to be used in publications / exhibitions.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC101; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 11" x 16" / Medium: ink / Support: trace
    Note: Three sketches of the GSD's Gund Hall, ink on trace for use in publications / exhibitions.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1993; Folder: CC102; / Quantity: 10 items / Dimensions: 11" x 16"; 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: ink / Support: trace; paper
    Note: Miscellaneous sketches of the GSD's Gund Hall to be used in publications / exhibitions.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: CC103; / Quantity: 37 items / Dimensions: 11" x 16"; 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: ink; xerographic copies / Support: trace; paper
    Note: Miscellaneous sketches of the GSD's Gund Hall, other Harvard buildings, and xerographic copies of photographs of GSD life to be used in publications / exhibitions. May have been used for an invitation card to a "Welcome Back Party" in 1995.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC104; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 11" x 14" / Medium: ink; photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Drawing, section of Gund Hall, to scale.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC105; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 11" x 14" / Medium: ink; photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Drawing, elevation of Robinson Hall, to scale.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC106; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 22" x 17" / Medium: photostats / Support: paper
    Note: Drawings (to scale), elevation of Robinson Hall and section of Gund Hall.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC107; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic reproduction / Support: paper
    Note: Xerographic copy of a detail of doors of Robinson Hall.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC108; / Quantity: 8 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: xerographic reproduction / Support: paper
    Note: Items in folders CF108 through CF115 from folder labeled "Noel's Random Sketch File." For use in publications and/or exhibitions.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC109; / Quantity: 27 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 11" x 17" / Medium: xerographic reproduction / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous xerographic reproductions for use in publications and/or exhibitions.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC110; / Quantity: 14 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 11" x 14"; 12" x 12" / Medium: xerographic reproduction; pencil / Support: paper; trace
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC111; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 11" x 17"; 11" x 14" / Medium: xerographic reproduction / Support: paper
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC112; / Quantity: 11 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 11" x 14" / Medium: xerographic reproduction; pencil / Support: paper; trace
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC113; / Quantity: 28 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 11" x 14" / Medium: xerographic reproduction / Support: paper
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 1997; Folder: CC114; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: photostat / Support: paper
    Note: Photostat from folder labeled "Dan Kiley images. Nov. 1997" (elevation of a house).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: CC115; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 17" / Medium: xerographic reproductions / Support: paper
    Note: Xerographic reproductions of a plan of Miller House, from folder labeled "Dan Kiley images."
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: CC116; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 17" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Spring 2000 issue of Gamut "a design publication fully produced and managed by students at the Harvard University Graduate School of Design."
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Exhibition Files, / Date(s): n.d. (1990s); Folder: CC117; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 9" x 17" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several copies of print poster with floor plans (with key of room names) of Gund Hall.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1990-1995; Folder: CC118; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 17" x 5-1/2"; 10" x 18"; 18" x 12" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Folders CF118 through CF122 from Bill Saunders' files.
    Note: Several posters of conferences and symposiums held at the GSD: Changing Scale: Recent Urban Projects (1990); Denaturalized Urbanity (1994); The Architecture of Science (1994); The New Planning Agenda (1995); Landscape Architecture, Social Ideology & the Politics of Place.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1993-1996; Folder: CC119; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 25" x 4-1/2"; 8-1/2" x 15"; 11" x 17" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several posters of conferences and symposiums held at the GSD: Environment, Sustainable Development and Design (1993); Designing Boston (1995); and Manufactuuring Cities: Competitive Advantage and the Urban Industrial Community (1996).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: CC120; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 24" x 11-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Poster of symposium held at the GSD: Exploring the Landscape Architecture of Richard Haag (1996).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1993-1994; Folder: CC121; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 17" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several posters of conferences and symposiums held at the GSD for the Symposium on Architectural Practices: Centers and Edges of Practice (1993); Constructs and Responsibilities in Architectural Practices: a Critical Exploration (1994); and Globalization of Design Practice (1994).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: CC122; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 11" x 17" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Poster for The Boston Bash, held at the Harvard Club in Boston (1995). "Dinner and dancing following the panel discussion."
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1992; Folder: CC123; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 7" x 7" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: "The Harvard Graduate School of Design: Directions for the Near Future" by Peter G. Rowe, an address delivered during Dean's Day at the GSD, October 24, 1992.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: CC124; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 7" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Booklet with lectures and exhibitions program for Fall 1994.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1992; Folder: CC125; / Quantity: 10 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several brochures of exhibitions organized by and held at the Graduate School of Design: New England Holocaust Memorial Competition: An American Process (1992); Prince of Wales Prize in Urban Design, 1993 (1993); United States Courthouse and Harborpark (1994); An Architecture for all Senses: The Work of Eileen Gray (1995); Exploring the Landscape Architecture of Richard Haag (1996); Roberto Burle Marx: Two Gardens in Brazil (1998); Representing Landscape Architecture: Four Centuries of Books and Images (1999); and Two Projects by Sir Norman Foster: The Bilbao Metro and the Carr'Art, Ns (1999).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1992; Folder: CC126; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 22" x 16" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Poster with program of lectures and exhibitions for Fall 1994.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1992; Folder: CC127; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8" x 6"; 11-1/2" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Exhibition catalogs of the work of Janet Echelman. Donated by the artist.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1999; Folder: CC128; / Quantity: 22 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence, emails, and other files related to the planning and organization of the 1999 GSD / ASLA Exhibition. Communications mainly between Mary Daniels, Brooke Hodge, and George Hargreaves. Includes exhibition list and wall text.
    Note: Also includes text "Fifty Years in Retrospect: Brief Account of the Origin and Development of the ASLA" by Bremmer W. Pond.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1999; Folder: CC129; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 11" x 14" / Medium: photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Includes photographs that were used in the GSD / ASLA Exhibition, 1999. Landscapes of sites, late 18th-early 19th century.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 2000-2001; Folder: CC130; / Quantity: 6 items / Dimensions: 24" x 16" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Posters with program of lectures, exhibitions, and conferences for Fall 2000 and for Spring 2001.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: CC131; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Directory Graduates Specializing in Real Estate 2000.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: CC132; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: The State of the Nation's Housing, Joint Center for Housing Studies, Harvard University, 2000.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1986-2007; Folder: CC133; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 6" x 5"; 8" x 8"; 5-1/2" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several brochures of exhibitions and conferences organized by and held at the Graduate School of Design: George Hargreaves: Specific Landscapes (1986); Projecting Beirut (1997); Exploring New Urbanism (1999); Manufactured Sites: A Landscape Architecture Exhibition on Site Technologies for Contemporary Practice (1998); Tsao & McKown: Serving Conscience (1999); Structure + Expression: Comme des Gars (2000); The 70s: The Formation of Contemporary Architectural Discourse (2000-2001) [held at Cornell University]; and Cities: X Lines (2007).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1957; Folder: CC134; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8"x 5-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Architectural Books and Drawings, 800-1800, selected and arranged from material in Harvard collections by Eduard F. Sekler.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1984; Folder: CC135; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 12" x 4" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Booklet for exhibition series Design Instruction at the Department of Architecture, by Dolf Schnebli. Traveling exhibition organized by ETH Zurich.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1976-1988; Folder: CC136; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 8" x 4"; 9" x 5-1/2"; 7-1/2" x 5-1/2"; 11" x 6"; 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several brochures of exhibitions and conferences organized by and held at the Graduate School of Design: Between Art and Industry: The Deutscher Werkbund (1976) [organized by Goethe Institute]; Transitions: a Photographic Documentary of Squatter Settlements (1978); Investigations in Architecture: Eisenman Studios at the GSD (1983-1985); Establishing a Threshold: Twelve Architectural Practices in Boston (1986); Ignazio Gardella (1986); Werner Seligmann: Recent Works (1986); Aga Khan Awards for Architecture (1986); Morphosis / Thom Mayne and Michael Rotondi (1988); Prince of Wales Prize in Urban Design, 1988; Emerging European Architects (1988); Eleanor Raymond Architect.
    Note: Also includes posters for lectures and exhibitions program for Fall 1981, Spring 1986, and Fall 1989.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1976; Folder: CC137; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Catalog for the exhibition Buildings for Books and Books for Building (1976) organized by Angela Giral, Librarian of the Frances Loeb Library.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1976; Folder: CC138; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8"; 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochure and item list for exhibition Bovisa, John Hejduk's project originally exhibited at the XVII Triennale of Milan, "Imaginary Cities" (1987).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1976-1986; Folder: CC139; / Quantity: 21 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 6" x 6" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Press releases, clippings, brochures and other miscellaneous materials about a couple of exhibitions held at the GSD: Transforming the American Garden: 12 New Landscape Designs (1986); French Aubusson Tapestries Today (1980); Works of Charles W. Moore (1982); and Rotch Travelling Scholarship: 1883-1983. Also includes xerographic copies of John Hejduk's "Berlin Masque."
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1987-1989; Folder: CC140; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several brochures of exhibitions and conferences organized by and held at the Graduate School of Design: Space Framed IV: Geraldine Erman and Michael Gitlin (1987); Amancio Williams (1987); Aerial View of the Landscape (1988); Gino Valle (1988); R.M. Schindler, Architect (1988); Alvaro Siza (1988); Kallmann, McKinnell & Wood (1988); George Hargreaves: Specific landscapes (1988); R.M. Schindler, Architekt (1988); Kristin Jones and Andrew Ginzel (1988); The Blue Ridge Parkway (1988); Luis Barragan: Architecture of Light, Color and Form (1989); Peter Walker (1989); Italian Gardens: Photographs from the Frances Loeb Library (1989); Rodolfo Machado and Jorge Silvetti: Buildings for Cities (1989); and Sigurd Lewerentz: Detail and Reflexion (1989).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1986-1987; Folder: CC141; / Quantity: 11 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several brochures of exhibitions and conferences organized by and held at the Graduate School of Design: Warren H. Manning (1986); Hugh Stubbins and His Associates: The First Fifty Years (1986); Massimo Scolari: Works 1971-1986 (1986); Bruce Graham (1986); Jennifer Bartlett (1987); Hiromi Fujii (1987); Tod Williams and Robert Mangurian (1987); Boris Podrecca (1987); Dolf Schnebli (1987).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1972; Folder: CC142; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures of exhibitions for the dedication of Frances Loeb Library. Includes Le Corbusier - Urbanisme and Cluny Exhibition.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1951; Folder: CC143; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 9" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Landscape Architecture (VF NAB 980 C) by the Department of Landscape Architecture, GSD, 1951. Published on occasion of the 50th anniversary of the department. Introduction by Bremmer Pond, edited by Lester Collins and Thomas Gillespie.
    Note: Papers in folders CF143 through CF147 may have been papers used in preparation of the 100th anniversary of the Department of Landscape Architectue.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1957-1958; Folder: CC144; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 11" x 17" / Medium: xerographic copies / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous copies of landscape problem statements of the 1950s. Includes also Landscape Architecture Education in Transition by Hideo Sasaki (1953).
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 1951-1953; Folder: CC145; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 7" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Numbers 1 and 3 of Forsite, published by the Department of City Planning and Landscape Architecture of the University of Illinois, 1951 and 1953.
  - Subseries CC: GSD Exhibitions -- Miscellaneous Materials, / Date(s): 2001; Folder: CC146; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 7" / Medium: computer printout; photographs / Support: paper; photographic paper